[
  {
    "itemName": "wq_seal",
    "roiFront": "244,181,40,40",
    "roiBack": "8,152,712,396",
    "description": "封印"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_done",
    "roiFront": "248,183,37,39",
    "roiBack": "107,147,570,389",
    "description": "勾号"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "trace_enable",
    "roiFront": "1097,588,101,70",
    "roiBack": "1097,588,101,70",
    "description": "一键追踪"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "tarce_disenable",
    "roiFront": "1091,586,108,70",
    "roiBack": "1091,586,108,70",
    "description": "取消追踪"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_box",
    "roiFront": "48,187,43,38",
    "roiBack": "20,137,100,397",
    "description": "奖励宝箱"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "trace_true",
    "roiFront": "173,187,28,29",
    "roiBack": "173,187,28,29",
    "description": "小号追踪"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "trace_false",
    "roiFront": "170,186,31,32",
    "roiBack": "170,186,31,32",
    "description": "小号不追踪"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "goto_1",
    "roiFront": "978,234,87,45",
    "roiBack": "978,234,87,45",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "goto_2",
    "roiFront": "979,305,88,43",
    "roiBack": "979,305,88,43",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "goto_3",
    "roiFront": "979,373,88,47",
    "roiBack": "979,373,88,47",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "goto_4",
    "roiFront": "979,447,87,42",
    "roiBack": "979,447,87,42",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "wq_check_task",
    "roiFront": "110,154,21,125",
    "roiBack": "73,122,69,459",
    "description": "判断是否还有任务"
  }
]